'''
Seperate py file that holds all the questions for the biology program. It is easily extendable by simply adding another number (with commas) and copying the same format.

To edit a question, change the text in the boxes next to 'question', 'answers' and put in the correct answer in 'correct_answer'.
'''
biology_questions = {
        0:
            {"question": "Which of the following is a species name?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Panthera Leo",
                  "b": "Canidae",
                  "c": "Protozoa",
                  "d": "Animal"},
             "correct_answer": "a"},
        1:
            {"question": "How many vital organs are there?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "4",
                  "b": "5",
                  "c": "6",
                  "d": "7"},
             "correct_answer": "b"},
        2:
            {"question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Vacuole",
                  "b": "Mitochondria",
                  "c": "Nucleus",
                  "d": "Chloroplast"},
             "correct_answer": "b"},
        3:
            {"question": "What does DNA stand for?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Deoxynucleic Acid",
                  "b": "Deribonucleix Acid",
                  "c": "Ribonucleic Acid",
                  "d": "Deoxyribonucleic Acid"},
             "correct_answer": "d"},
        4:
            {"question": "What is low blood sugar called?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Hyperglycemia",
                  "b": "Hypoglycemia",
                  "c": "Heteroglycemia",
                  "d": "Homoglycemia"},
             "correct_answer": "b"},
        5:
            {"question": "What is speciation through geographic isolation called?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Parapatric",
                  "b": "Peripatric",
                  "c": "Allopatric",
                  "d": "Patopatric"},
             "correct_answer": "c"},
        6:
            {"question": "How many chromosomes does a human have?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "23",
                  "b": "10",
                  "c": "39",
                  "d": "46"},
             "correct_answer": "d"},
        7:
            {"question": "What is the most recent ancestor of Homo Sapiens?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Homo Ergaster",
                  "b": "Homo Erectus",
                  "c": "Homo Neaderthalensis",
                  "d": "Homo Heidelbergensis"},
             "correct_answer": "d"},
        8:
            {"question": "Which is an essential element in the human body?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Sulfur",
                  "b": "Lead",
                  "c": "Cadmium",
                  "d": "Bromine"},
             "correct_answer": "a"},
        9:
            {"question": "What is the term for non-directional response in animals?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Kinesis",
                  "b": "Taxes",
                  "c": "Tropism",
                  "d": "Nasty"},
             "correct_answer": "a"},
        10:
            {"question": "What is not a kind of RNA?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "mRNA",
                  "b": "tRNA",
                  "c": "kRNA",
                  "d": "rRNA"},
             "correct_answer": "c"},
        11:
            {"question": "A pigment that determines human hair colour is called?",
             "answers":
                 {"a": "Melatonin",
                  "b": "Chlorophyll",
                  "c": "Melanin",
                  "d": "Auxin"},
             "correct_answer": "c"}
        }
